iabrasive.com 2019-02-25

# Privacy Policy - iAbrasive.com

## Privacy Policy

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of iAbrasive.com (the “Site”, “we” or “our”). 

By using this Site, you approve and agree to our Privacy Policy set forth below. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and iAbrasive.com which by use of this Site you agree to accept. 

### 1\. THE TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

  * 1.1 Registration Information:  
At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to fill out a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business (" **Registration Information** "). 
  * 1.2 Publishing Information:  
If you submit any information to iAbrasive.com to be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to our Company Directory, Trade/Product/Service Listings, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information so long as they do not pertain to personal information (" **Publishing Information** "). 
  * 1.3 Buyer Information:  
We record and retain records of buying and browsing activities on our platform including but not limited to IP addresses, browsing patterns, buyer behavioral patterns, buyer contact details, buyer profiles and so on (" **Buyer Information** "). 
  * 1.4 Payment Information:  
If you establish a credit account with us or our providers or if you purchase a product or service from iAbrasive.com or other registered users of the Site or other vendors available through the Site, we may collect additional information, which may include billing information, credit card numbers and expiration dates and tracking information from cheques or money orders (" **Payment Information** "). 
  * 1.5 Account Activities Information:  
We record and retain the records of your Account activities when you use the iAbrasive.com services. If you make sale and purchase transactions online through iAbrasive.com's web-based transaction platform, we also collect information related to such transactions including the types and specifications of the goods, pricing and delivery information, any trade dispute records (" **Account Activities Information** "). 
  * 1.6 Statistical Information.  
In addition, we gather aggregate statistical information about our Site and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions and unique visitors, etc. (" **Statistical Information** "). 
  * 1.7 Marketing Information:  
From time to time, we gather information about our Users and prospective users during trade shows, marketing events and other functions for follow up marketing purposes (" **Marketing Information** "). 
  * 1.8 Personal Information:  
From time to time, our Users may disclose personal data deliberately or inadvertently including without limitation to personal identifiers such as name, email address, tel/fax number, and IP address of individuals in the course of using the Site (" **Personal Information** "). 
  * 1.9 Collected Information:  
Registration Information, Publishing Information, Buyer Information, Payment Information, Account Activities Information, Statistical Information, Marketing Information, Personal Information and any information we may collect from you through the use of Cookies (see Section 4 below), or from our affiliates or from other parties or through any other means, shall collectively be referred to as (" **Collected Information** "). 

### 2\. HOW WE USE THE COLLECTED INFORMATION

  * 2.1 General: 

We use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you. 

We use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. 

We share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users. 
  * 2.2 Registration Information: 

We use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services in which iAbrasive.com determines that you might be interested. 

Specifically, we use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, product alerts, and communications relevant to your use of our Site, if you choose to receive these as indicated at the time of registration. 

We generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. 

  * 2.3 Publishing Information: 

All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. 

Any Publishing Information that you disclose to iAbrasive.com becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. 

You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to us. 

  * 2.4 Buyer Information:  
We use Buyer Information to provide value-added services to our members including without limitation to providing buying pattern and buying behavioral data to our members to facilitate marketing initiatives and decision making. 
  * 2.5 Payment Information:  
iAbrasive.com will share your Payment Information with banks or vendors relevant to the transaction in order to enable transactions to be completed. In addition, iAbrasive.com may use Payment Information to determine your credit-worthiness, and in the process of such determination, iAbrasive.com may make such Payment Information available to banks or credit agencies. While iAbrasive.com has in place up-to-date technology and internal procedures to guard your Payment Information against intruders, there is no guarantee that such technology or procedure can eliminate all of the risks of theft, loss or misuse. iAbrasive.com shall not be liable to you or any other person for any damages that might result from unauthorized use, publication, disclosure or any other misuse of Payment Information, including credit card information. 
  * 2.6 Statistical Information: 

We use Statistical Information to help diagnose problems with and maintain our computer servers, to manage our Site, and to enhance your site and services based on the usage pattern data we receive. 

We generate reports and analysis based on the Statistical Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. We provide Statistical Information to third parties, but when we do so, we do not provide them any Personal Identifying Information. 
  * 2.7 Personal Information:  
We facilitate e-commerce between business-to-business and our services should not be used by individual consumers or for personal use. Should Personal Information be disclosed for business purposes in the course of using our Site and services, such Personal Information may be used to provide value-added services to our members to facilitate including without limitation marketing initiatives and contacts. Uses of any Personal Information by any of our members are subject to privacy laws in the respective jurisdictions of our members. Each of our members is solely responsible for observing applicable laws and regulations in its respective jurisdictions to ensure that all use of the Site and Services are in compliance with the same. Each of our members is expressly prohibited from using any Personal Information for illegal activities including without limitation to spamming. 

### 3\. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

  * 3.1  
Members who sign up for iAbrasive service may promote themselves by listing a profile along with product/service listings that are then made visible to other members and the rest of the internet community. At this point the promoting member exposes Personal Identifying Information for public viewing. The promoting member has full control over the information that is being published and may change it at any time. 
  * 3.2 

We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Identifying Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of iAbrasive.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

We also reserve the right to disclose Personal Identifying Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority. 
  * 3.3   
If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of Use Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User's Personal Identifying Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to iAbrasive.com or others. 
  * 3.4   
We will never share, sell, rent or trade Personal Identifying Information with third parties for their promotional purposes. 

### 4\. HOW WE USE COOKIES

  * Cookies are nuggets of information that are placed by a Site in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the Site, to deliver content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on the Site, you may be given the option to save your display name and password on your computer; we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliates and other companies. 
  * Some of our advertisers may serve you cookies as well; we do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. 
  * We may also use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the Site. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith. 
  * If you don’t want any cookies, your web browser almost certainly includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Site may not function properly. 

### 5\. MINORS

  * The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. 
  * However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. 
  * If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information. 

### 6\. HOW WE TREAT SECURITY AND NOTIFICATION

  * 6.1   
We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information. 
  * 6.2   
As a Registered User, your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. 
  * 6.3   
No data transmission over the internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases, and by using the Site you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the Site. 

### 7\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

  * Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. 
  * You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. 
  * If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact iAbrasive.com in writing (at the address set below in "Contact Us") and specifically request that iAbrasive.com return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in iAbrasive.com's possession. 

### 8\. ACCESS AND UPDATING OF YOUR INFORMATION

  * Users may access, view and edit posted Information at any time and as often as necessary through Users' Account with iAbrasive.com. 
  * To update or correct such information, please log into your account and make the changes. 
  * If you wish to unsubscribe to our email communications and/or de-list your company profile please advise us of this by communicating with us by means of following "Contact Us". 

### 9\. CONTACT US

  * If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact: 

iAbrasive.com  
Tel: +86-15138655293  
Email: info@iabrasive.com
